let naQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who is the player in the NBA logo?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Michael Jordan",
    choiceB: "LeBron James",
    choiceC: "Ray Allen",
    choiceD: "Jerry West",
    correct: "D"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all time leading scoring in the NBA?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Kareem Abdul Jabar",
    choiceB: "Larry Bird",
    choiceC: "LeBron James",
    choiceD: "Scottie Pippen",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "The Montreal Canadians have the most Stanley Cups in the NHL, but how many do they have?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "24",
    choiceB: "15",
    choiceC: "8",
    choiceD: "19",
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the acclaimed GOAT of hockey? Commonly referred to as 'The Great One'",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Alex Ovechkin",
    choiceB: "Sydney Crosby",
    choiceC: "Wayne Gretzky",
    choiceD: "Gordie Howe",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "Earning just above $43 million a year, who is currently the highest paid MLB player?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Aaron Judge",
    choiceB: "Max Scherzer",
    choiceC: "Shohei Otahni",
    choiceD: "Mike Trout",
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "Barry Bonds hold the record for most HRs in a season with how many?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "61",
    choiceB: "73",
    choiceC: "64",
    choiceD: "58",
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the only kicker to ever win the NFL MVP award?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Justin Tucker",
    choiceB: "Dan Bailey",
    choiceC: "Billy Cundiff",
    choiceD: "Mark Moseley",
    correct: "D"
  },
  {
    question: "Despite making the superbowl, the 2011 Patriots only defeated one team with a winning record, who was it?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "Baltimore Ravens",
    choiceB: "New York Giants",
    choiceC: "Detroit Lions",
    choiceD: "San Diego Chargers",
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "Michael Phelps holds the record for most Olympic gold medals with how many?",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "18",
    choiceB: "28",
    choiceC: "23",
    choiceD: "17",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "The USWNT is the most successful international women's soccer team in the world with how many Women's World Cup titles",
    imgSrc: ,
    choiceA: "5",
    choiceB: "4",
    choiceC: "6",
    choiceD: "8",
    correct: "B"
  },
]